hey everyone thanks for listening to the
grow your life podcast my name is
jeremiah krakowski and in this podcast
we talk about ways for you to grow in
your life in your business to build your
coaching and course business now today i
want to help you know how to create a
coaching program if you've never done
coaching before maybe you've created
courses or maybe you've thought about
hey maybe i can make money in this
coaching thing i want to walk you
through that that's what this week's
podcast episode is all about now
why should you listen to me well i've
been in the industry of online courses
and coaching for the last
19 years which is incredible it helping
people sell their programs online now i
got my start doing videos
websites and funnels but i quickly
learned how to do the sales and
marketing side of it i taught myself
copywriting ended up going on to
building a company alongside my mom that
was over 20 million dollars in the
coaching and course space and some of
you know my mom sandy krakowski and now
i help mentor course graders coaches
authors trainers and even consultants on
how to
get more clients attract their dream
clients and grow their course and
coaching businesses how to use the tools
of social media and advertising as well
as organic traffic like blogging and
social media to scale and grow things
and live a life that is something that
they love that is not stressful
that pays them a heck of a lot of money
and is extremely fun and enjoyable to do
and and fulfilling because of the impact
that you have the truth is this coaches
change the world
they do
coaches
change the world and
when you start a business as a coach
as a course creator and you get into
this industry and you want to create a
coaching business you might wonder well
why are you saying courses i want to do
coaching i'm going to explain that to
you for a second i have a methodology
about coaching that involves using both
okay
my methodology is this is that we want
to figure out how to
work with a target type of client
and so because of that you're going to
end up
coaching people with very similar
problems
and so the reason why courses are part
of coaching the way that i do it and
they kind of mix together is if you find
yourself basically
finding and reaching the same solution
with the same clients over and over
again and there's a pattern you turn
that into a course and it supplements
your coaching so they can self-study
based off of hundreds of people that
you've coached
what you've learned through your courses
and then your coaching supplements that
for hands-on interaction and you walking
people through things and there's
different ways of coaching there's
different ways of doing things sometimes
there's more of the expert coach
approach which is kind of the one that i
take it's where i'm an expert in
marketing and
getting people to become customers of
coaches
and getting people to become customers
of course creators and using the
internet to do that and then you have
the the traditional coach which is also
a great thing by the way and and i work
with both
and so the traditional coach more
focuses on how do we ask questions to
pull out of people
what they need help with and and i use a
hybrid of those too
oftentimes when i'm coaching
i don't share my expertise
without permission of who i'm working
with
and oftentimes i'm coaching them on an
industry that i have no knowledge about
and that's the cool thing about coaching
you don't need to be an expert on the
industry that they're in so i coach
people that are coaches course creators
authors trainers and consultants but the
industries that they work in are usually
not
the coaching course creation
industry space that's we got people that
do music
fitness
health
spiritual coaching uh
life coaching
uh multiple people that are life coaches
um
network marketing coaches like they help
people that are in direct sales
um
you name it
any sort of thing that people want to
improve their life on
you can make a coaching program on and
that's a big
key nugget for you is when creating a
coaching program
you want to identify what is the result
that somebody needs to
transform
into
in order for you to successfully bring
them the result that you can
with your program the result that you
can with your coaching you're selling
results to people
you're selling the outcome that they get
you're selling that you can walk people
through a process
to reach
that outcome and if you're on the online
version of this you're watching i'm
going to share with you something
so i have a new course that i actually
released called transformational
coaching made simple it's the right way
to do coaching that transforms people's
lives while building a profitable
stress-free business that you'll love
without selling your time or energy even
if you've never coached before and so i
walk you through my process my
methodology
let's
talk about this so like i said i've been
in the industry for 19 years right
i've been coaching for about six years
and so my experience as a coach
is a lot less than my experience as a
marketer and a salesperson
and so i
found my background helping other expert
coaches
authors and course creators
get more customers okay
and so and we were able to scale
businesses to multiple tens of millions
of dollars doing this
we have clients right now that were
helping scale their businesses to
multiple tens of millions of dollars
half a million dollars a month
is that's right around six million a
year
and that was just like testing something
that client is easily going to go to
over 10 to 20 million a year in the next
12 to 16 to 18 months
and they were just starting where most
of you were at
making
10 000 a month
three years ago
that was my client rick pino that we
work with
and so what i'm telling you is this is
that you can start with that's why i put
on my website right here i mentor course
creators coaches trainers consultants
and authors to make 20 000 per month
the the plus symbol there is is that
it's you're not lit i don't limit myself
to 20k i help people get to that 20k
really fast and then scale way beyond it
grow way beyond it to build a profitable
business using online direct response
marketing now we're not going to really
talk a lot about the marketing today i
have a ton of courses a ton of podcast
episodes about marketing but what i
realize is i don't actually have a whole
lot of episodes about coaching programs
i need to and so that's what this
episode is for that's why i'm talking
with you today about this and so while
i'm sharing i'd love for you to
leave some questions what this inspires
in you i'll be sure to kind of check
some of your questions we're streaming
this live on my social media by the way
if you follow me on my social media and
you're listening to the recording of
this i do go live towards the end of the
week not sure when it's kind of based on
when i feel like it
thursdays fridays or saturdays and
record live my podcast episodes and so
you get to interact live with me in the
studio
while i'm recording this
and you get to ask me questions on the
screen while i'm doing this which is
awesome okay so
in starting your coaching program
what is the problem that you solve
who do you solve it for
what result do you deliver
what is the pain point of the person
that you solve the problem of and where
are those people stuck
so i want you to answer those questions
i want you to answer those questions for
me
write them down
answer them
what is the problem you solve
who is the person that has that problem
describe them
where do they go
what do they do throughout the day how
do they operate
what fears do they have what worries
what struggles what frustrations
you see what i'm saying
and then what pain do they have because
of that
what result do you deliver that aligns
with the goals that they have
so the result that i deliver is i help
people grow
their course and coaching business
using social media and artificial
intelligence
even if they're not super techy
or understand using technology
okay
and how to scale that
to six figures and even seven figures
that's the result that i deliver
to my clients and that's the goal
that my clients have and when there's an
alignment there
we can create a coaching relationship
and so you want to identify
who are you serving
what is your coaching program about
what is the main problem
where are they stuck and why are they
stuck psychologically
why are they so stuck
if you don't have answers to these
questions now
you'll get them eventually
by talking to other people
by learning from people that you're
coaching
a way that you can accelerate this
process is getting around the people
that are your target coaching client
spending time around them
spending time around the people
that you can most likely help
immersing yourself in the world of your
target customer and i have a whole lot
of videos about the target customer
we have to understand psychologically
the person
that is most likely to become our client
what makes them tick
and then you learn how to communicate
with them
you learn how to interact with them what
are the sacred cows that they get
offended by
what are their
big drivers what are their personality
types what are their personality
uniquenesses what are their main goals
and what are their subconscious goals
and so when you understand this you
build a a profile
of your target customer and you build
your coaching program
around that target customer and the
result that you do
and your methodology okay
so we have to understand what are our
methods
so for me my methods are social media
i had a lady the other day say jeremiah
can you show me how to build a coaching
program without social media i said i'm
sorry
you're in the wrong place because that's
not me i do not not use social media
if you're listening to me and don't want
to use social media
you're in the wrong place
everything i do is based off social
media
there's people that teach you how to not
use social media like steve chandler
author of the prosperous coach
okay and by the way there's some great
nuggets in steve chandler's books steve
chandler's books 30 seven ways to to
grow your coaching practice has got some
great strategies
i highly recommend that book on amazon
but the prosperous coach is about how to
do it without social media
i wasn't a big fan of the book because
i'm like it's literally the opposite of
everything that i do but you know what
they're getting coaching clients now
does that mean that steve chandler's way
is better than mine or that mine is
better than his no and that is a huge
distinction that i want you to
understand
is that in the world there is not one
single best way to do
everything now what i will show you is
the best way to use social media to do
it
steve chandler will show you
i believe after listening to him the
best way
to build a coaching program without
social media
and we're not talking about making tons
of content like we're talking about
making
one video
a day on social media and making one
advertisement video one or two ad videos
a week that's usually what most of our
clients do now as they make one video a
day when they're getting started until
they have a team that can help edit
content for them and can analyze their
content
starting with that is enough
to get you going
and what's cool is now we have tools
like jasper.ai which we're using for
literally everything that we do
jasper.ai is a tool that uses artificial
intelligence to write your content your
facebook ads your copy your social media
your website your product listings
everything
using artificial intelligence i actually
just worked on a name for a new
product that this week
that i'm working on a couple new
products i got like four or five of them
that are in the works that i'm building
now
that are gonna serve you guys
around your offers your copy you're
gonna get more support with me
i'm i will i'm to be launching a group
coaching program here soon
you heard it here first right now
listening to this
i do one-on-one coaching but we're going
to be doing a low-cost group coaching
and for those of you that follow me
right now and have bought all my courses
you will get the lowest possible rate
before the rest of the public gets it
which is awesome
i'm going to make sure to honor people
that have been with me for a long time
but we use jasper
to do
everything
jasper helps us write
all of our copy and you can actually get
a free trial of jasper if you go to my
instagram
uh i probably should put it at the top
of my website free trial of jasper
um
but i'll put it i'll put it in the
description of this podcast episode once
it's uploaded live and you can grab it
and it's the single greatest software
application
that i've ever seen on planet earth
to write high quality copy with
artificial intelligence
it it does creative stories it helps you
write your social media content your
blog posts facebook ads
headlines captions
marketing angles
email subject like it's it's insane
they have this new one called the
paragraph generator it generates a whole
paragraph
in really good english
based off of
just a few inputs and their boss mode is
even crazier because it's so much faster
you can literally do everything in a
couple minutes so i'm a huge fan of
jasper ai i'm an affiliate of theirs i
promote their product because i believe
in it because i believe that it's one of
the greatest products that has ever been
created
in the history of online products and
i'm not even joking
i had a dream for this product to exist
for years and when the creators of
jasper created the product i was like
whoa
i'm blown away by this okay
and so
that's for free on your marketing side
of things but what's really cool is
jasper will also help you identify
what angles to do with your coaching
program so what i do is we load up into
jasper
exactly
what the target customer is dealing with
their problems
and their frustrations in fact i'm going
to walk you through how we do this
to create
the angle of our coaching program so
when you're just getting started you
might have a baseline
and we can use ai to actually figure out
how to communicate that and express that
much faster so let's say that you help
single
single women without kids
by choice
who want to be
more knowledgeable
about
how to powerfully
and successfully
live their life
operate in corporate america
and stand powerfully
and unashamed
every single day okay
so that's who it's for
okay what are some
of
the problems and frustrations
these women experience
and we're asking the ai to generate it
some of the problems they experience is
feeling isolated feeling like they don't
fit in and don't have a lot of support
they can also feel a lack of knowledge
and resources available to them awesome
this is the ai that's generating this
and this is based off of somebody that i
talked to
uh that is actually creating a coaching
program around this so this is cool i'm
actually going to send her this video
because this video is actually going to
be a training for her to help her create
her offer much faster so this that so
that's i do a lot of training for my
coaching clients that pay me that i work
with that do one-on-one coaching with me
you can find out about my one-on-one
coaching at my website
jeremiahkowski.com where i will come
alongside you
and we will build together
your business
and i'm actually raising the price on
this
uh on tuesday to seventy five hundred
dollars to do this or you can make six
payments of one thousand two hundred and
fifty dollars a month for twelve
sessions twelve hour sessions but the
sale is for five thousand dollars you
can get those twelve sessions
or a thousand dollars a month for six
months
and you get all my courses when you do
that
as well by the way i'm doing if you're
watching this now i'm doing a free trial
or a dollar trial sorry not a free trial
probably never going to do a free trial
but you can actually try all my courses
for one dollar for 30 days
until tuesday april 5th
and if you like them you just pay
monthly know it zero percent apr no
credit check
80 284 a month to get all my courses or
one payment of 497 and that's all my
courses
on topics like
transformational coaching made simple
easy course creation blueprint
social media content creation made easy
irresistible offers how to create offers
that people can't say no to
social media ads that work
website building made easy if you're
just getting started building your
website this is my first course that i
actually made
three years ago and it's still one of
the best courses on squarespace out
there
those courses by themselves are 497
bucks but until tuesday you can actually
get that dollar trial which is awesome
so if you're watching this on monday you
got till tomorrow to do that okay
and so what we're able to do is we're
able to go to jasper and actually type
this in so we have we have who the
person is
what their problems are
what is the biggest pain
the women above experience
so you're actually asking it like a
writing assistant what it is the biggest
pain
is feeling feeling frustrated in a lack
of knowledge
describe the frustration
and feelings of isolation
these women above feel
okay so it's repeating that so that's
where the ai is kind of like it's kind
of dumb right
it's like okay it keeps cycling the same
the same issue over and over again
um what are the first
frustrations
and
feelings
the women above have
we're gonna put this in here
yeah
there you go that's great that's really
good
so this really describes i think
that the type of person right here
what is the goal of the women above
they want to be more knowledgeable
they also want validation for their
choice of a solo lifestyle without kids
and
how can a coach
help these women
get
their results
okay
supportive community awesome so now
we're going to write some headlines this
is jasper coming up with our program the
challenges of being a single woman how
to support
i find support the benefits of being an
independent woman today how to stand out
as a single woman in the crowd
10 things every single woman should have
in her arsenal the joys of living single
skeptical questions is the idea of being
happy as a single woman false
aren't there any idea
aren't you still individual if you live
yep
single women are powerful and unafraid
they don't need a man to validate them
to make them happy
okay
it's not just the wedding that's weird
um sometimes the ai is off single
independent and unafraid
and so we're able to do is we're able to
go through all this and create a profile
for our copy and our offers
off of this
okay
but what's cool is this actually helps
us create what our coaching program is
all about because we're understanding
more
what the customer is experiencing
um that was weird
write a fictional story about the
customer above i was a single woman felt
so frustrated and all alone i didn't fit
in i didn't know where to find support
but i found a coach who was able to help
me with the resources and support she
helped me feel validated and understood
and also helped me
as a coach you can also help
community you don't need you don't have
to answer
to anyone you can find your own happy
yep perfect
awesome
so right there that really describes
the type of women and here's the thing
so i haven't really talked much with
this this new client
but um
about this beyond here
so what she would do is she would fill
in if any of that information is
inaccurate according to
what she knows about that target
customer right
she would change some of that language
before going to the next step
and so and then what you do is you go to
the next step you use
what's called an epiphany bridge
and so an epiphany bridge helps write a
back story
about
the person
who we're talking about
and so the back story
is
is where we find we reach that sort of
epiphany
of
finding the solution and then what we're
doing is we reverse engineer how that
person found a solution
and that's what you build your coaching
program around
and then you are already 10 steps ahead
with your marketing because you're able
to use all of this language
to write your marketing and to describe
and to create your offers
and to create exactly what you do and
how you help people
okay
and so we're just going through here
we're telling the ai to generate this
looking for
okay we're gonna remove that
then we're gonna put this right here
okay
so now we have that and now we're gonna
go back to
the idea factory and i have another one
that i like to do too it's called the
hero's journey outline so the hero's
journey outline creates story arcs and
developments
about the person it can help you even
create children's books and comic books
that way which i'm actually using to
create comic books so i'm actually
taking this process running it through
the ai here and helping write stories
for comic books
using artificial intelligence
okay and so now and so this is all we're
doing is we're just based off of that
simple line of information that we knew
about the customer
single women
without kids by choice who want to be
more knowledgeable about how to
powerfully and successfully live their
life operate in court and stay
powerfully unshamed okay and so then
that built out a lot of this and then
we're letting the ai refine it like it's
chipping away at the stuff that's not
working for us okay so finding a
community of supportive women is a very
important need
is really the fact that it's like at
this tribe
right
and that's where you're you're so like
for instance
the lady who has this program she would
actually structure her program to be
sort of the like a tribe of independent
strong powerful single women without
kids
and it's very niche it's very unique
okay
it's very niche it's very unique
and here's where i would i would um
i would hone this in some more
so i would copy this to the content
brief
right here
and then we go back down here
and have it
right pass
for the above
that doesn't make sense
let's remove that
yeah
right pass for the above
when you're a single woman it can be
hard to find resources in the port you
might feel like you don't fit in
that no one understands what you're
going through
and so this is how we're able to really
communicate
the value of our program and now like
you see we're getting a clear picture of
what we would build a program around
so we would build a community from day
one
you need a community
there's a community built in without a
community like you know i would not do
courses first i would do a group
community first for this type of thing
okay
resources support encouragement
that provides validation
place to ask questions a safe space
a place that they won't feel judged
right
okay and so that's what this is and so
now here's what we we can do
too that's really fun
write some youtube video titles based on
the above
yeah
cool so she called it a
counter culture
cafe which i thought was pretty cool
um
and so based off of this
we're able to
write the name of a live event
based on the above so this is the
process that we go through when we do
this right
single women without kids live event
yeah so that's what it is
and so now that's that's how we were
able to figure out okay based off of who
this is
what type of program should we create
so you can even say what would the
features of a coaching program that
helps the above
include
resources
community coaching experience with
understanding and empathy
assistance and it would be
affordable okay
and so we were able to package that all
together to figure out exactly what
program to create
so we would so we would include
all of this as the features of that
program
write a feature to benefit for the above
so this is where we convert it from
standard features to benefits spend less
time oh no that's that's a that's a
glitch
that's also a glitch
hmm
it's glitching out
we'll do it right here
it goes based off of what's above it so
that's why you gotta like
coaching program
there you go
get help from a coach that understands
your struggles find resources and
support from a community of women
how to find a community of supportive
women look for groups and forums what
specifically ask your friends check a
local community search online when all
else fell start your own and that's what
my coaching client is doing right there
that's great
it's really good
so that's how we're able to come up with
using jasper
what
your coaching program is and this is
right around 2000 words right here
um
jasper the trial gives you 10 000 words
for free you can use it to come up with
your copy and your coaching program and
so that's what we do is we reverse
engineer who the person is what their
problem is
what we can solve for them and then we
figure out okay
the community aspect how do we get
people into that community right
and so these are pricing models so you
can use a monthly membership
subscription model and you can set
something like that up with thinkific
so thinkific is one of the best
platforms that i know to use for this
you could also just use it as simple as
patreon
patreon is another way that you could do
that
the best platform and the most expensive
is kajabi
for your your course your community
your coaching see so they work with all
of this turn knowledge into income
your podcast things like that your
trainings
your blogging
that's what kajabi does okay
but most you can set up a website with
squarespace
very easily very simply at a low cost to
grow your business online
create a website
see what i'm saying
and so you set that up
you make an offer
you attract people to you
you make some social media content that
talks about all these problems
by the way jasper has a really cool tool
um that was me writing some content
right there
for one of my programs
so jasper has this really cool function
called create engaging questions
and so then if you wonder okay what
should i
say
on my social media content right
what are some social media posts that i
can create we say write some engaging
questions for the above
how does it you feel about being a
single woman do you think there's
something wrong with it what are
challenges you face does you feel like
you're in control of your life what are
some of the benefits write some engaging
questions about the
about the coaching program above
what are the benefits of coaching
okay
write some engaging questions about the
problems that the person who seeks out
the coaching program above has
not sure that that worked
what are the most difficult challenges
faced do you feel unsupported in your
life how do you handle setbacks and
failures when they happen so see these
are social media posts now uh write a
creative story based on the questions
above
okay
and so this even can become a social
media post you can make it based off of
one of the questions
and so the then the ai will literally go
to work to generate
this type of content
for you
automatically
it's pretty awesome
and so then you can use that
the social media content attracts people
to you to become your customer
and then you can make offers to them
okay so then we would use an offer
creation stack
where we go
write some
youtube video titles
based on the above
oh that's not it so we use the the word
youtube video titles because youtube
video titles also make for really great
uh offer names
how to be a strong single woman how do
single women overcome challenges finding
support as a single woman when nobody
sees you
well nobody sees you yep
that's it that's what we use
and then we build out
an offer right here
based off of all of this right here the
standard benefits
okay
so we have this these are some of the
benefits that somebody will get
when they sign up for your offer
right there
and then we use the story right here
write a story about someone who went
through the coaching program above
and the results
they experienced
okay so you can use some of this copy
right here
i faced challenges and setbacks but
through it all i learned what to do
in life and then this is where you
personalize it with them
you're able to use this
right here
talk about what the person
above wants to do with a student
of this live
training
i want to help you
ace learn how to be strong and
independent
no longer do you have to deal with being
alone and in isolation so we flip the
copy
join me for a live training that i'm
doing
that i'm host
training that i'm hosting on
xyz date
and then
qualify the offer
above based on the coaches
experience
and share their bio
there we go
this free training is designed for we
want to navigate
it's based off my years of experience
provides women with the support they
need to be successful some of the
some
of what you will learn in this free
training
includes
finding resources
includes discovering how to
yep
there we go
and we would get more specific with this
as well but that becomes an offer and so
then that offer you can direct people
from your social media content to this
offer it can be a free training that you
run you can do it on video and you teach
what you learn to people
and then you
tell them they can schedule a call with
you you can use an app like calendly
right here to schedule a call with you
at the end of a training
and so i use that over my website people
can schedule a 45-minute discovery call
with me if they're serious about
one-on-one coaching
okay
and so these are my available times and
so somebody can schedule that and then
what i have is when somebody clicks this
i have an intake form
what are your 90 day goals what would
you say are the most important areas
that you need to reach those goals
what are the number one thing preventing
you
what have you tried before
what has worked what hasn't worked
what other coaching programs or
trainings have you taken in the past
any other things that i should be aware
of are you willing to invest 1500 a
month which is a thousand a month for
coaching and 500 for advertising
if they say no i'll probably tell them
hey coaching's not a good fit check out
this other program right if when you
launch a group program
you you can
take this intake form and and you don't
even need to have this investment
question because the cost would be
probably under 50 or 100 a month 100
bucks a month would be cool because they
could invest in a year with you and
here's how i would do a coaching program
is you offer the program for a thousand
dollars
okay and that might challenge you
because you might have a belief that you
can't charge that much for what you do
here's how you do it you offer it one
time payment of a thousand bucks or they
can make payments with zero percent
interest
for 82.84 for 12 months
you see what i'm saying or do 997. and
so then they're able to make payments
that are under 100 bucks a month to join
this community with you this community
of powerful strong independent women
that are not in a relationship that
don't need a man
that don't have kids
and you're able to cultivate that
together so that's the example of that
and this whole methodology by the way
translates to every single niche
and industry
and so you're able to use this to write
copy
for coaching programs
to launch them out there okay so that's
your group
program
depending on the price that they can
afford
what you're going to end up doing though
is you want to have some kind of a value
ladder mechanism to or what you're going
to notice is okay
what do those people
that i'm coaching
what do they need more help with so you
might have your large community right
that's the big circle here but then the
circles get smaller the deeper we go in
and you're going to niche down to people
that really need help so i have my
courses right
over my website my courses
they all talk about
what course creators and coaches need to
get more results
and then you can buy my courses from me
and and then i have my one-on-one
coaching and so my one-on-one coaching
is where i come alongside you and help
you with all of that stuff but it's
built on the foundation
of what the courses teach
it's help it's to help take people
to a further next
level
okay
and so then what you do is you build all
of your marketing around that to create
a feedback loop
and so what you're doing is you're
constantly looking for feedback
from your target customer you want them
to give you feedback about what they're
dealing with about what they like about
your program about what they want to
learn about what their goals are
okay
and so then with that you create
new courses when you find a pattern
you create new social media content when
you find a pattern
and then you you end up structuring your
offers
for your coaching this offer gets more
and more specific as time goes on and
you really niche down and the more you
niche down
the better
your copy
gets the better your conversions get the
better
you're able
to connect with your target customer and
so this is how we're able to spin up and
launch coaching programs and courses
on autopilot basically with very little
effort with very little time spent with
very little need to have to to do a lot
of technical stuff by using the
artificial intelligence to be able to do
that
you get it
listen if you have some questions on
this i'd love to talk with you
i'd love to help you and listen if you
have more questions about how do i build
this out as a coaching program again
think about taking me up on the offer of
all of my courses the dollar trial and
you can go through specifically this
course
right here transformational coaching
made simple where i walk you through
everything that you need to know to
successfully become a world-class coach
even if you've never coached before to
build a profitable coaching program that
can have
impact that you can be proud of
and you can read more of it on my
website right here transformational
coaching made simple
stress-free profitable coaching is a
reality when you follow what i teach in
this program by the way all of this was
also written with jasper
literally
coaching isn't about telling people what
to do it's about learning to ask the
right questions
and so i was able to take my knowledge
and then jasper writes all of these
offers and creates them for me in record
time
and that's how we're building our
business we're using artificial
intelligence
to our advantage
ai is the engine that drives everything
when we run ads we use ai as well
we're using the algorithms on tick tock
facebook and instagram mostly those
three
we still post on linkedin and twitter
but tiktok facebook and instagram are
the algorithms that we use the most okay
and we train the artificial intelligence
on these platforms which by the way
i've managed over 8 million
in paid ads working with my clients
generating five to 10x row us
return on the ad spend
and so i show you in this course how to
use ai
to run
ad campaigns
and so my friends
as a coach
as a trainer
as somebody that wants to have an impact
on people's lives
what's stopping you that's the question
that i got to ask you
and the the answer to that is i know
already if you listen to this podcast
and you've made it all the way through
this podcast to right now
the only thing stopping you is not the
knowledge of how to do it because i
literally just gave you the blueprint
of what to do to at least get started
you have no excuse to say i don't know
how to get started no
you don't
because i broke it down for you step by
step
you don't have to figure out what comes
after that
you don't have to figure out
how you're going to manage
these people
my friends that's called a mindset issue
when we let overwhelm talk us out of
doing what we're called to do that is a
mental issue and it has nothing to do
with knowledge and strategy
i made a post on my social media
yesterday that says that overthinking is
the biggest waste of human energy
trust yourself
make a decision and gain more experience
there's no such thing as perfect
and you can't think your way into
perfection
just take action perfectionism
is a lie
perfectionism
is a complete misconception there's no
such thing as perfect
and so you have to divorce the idea that
you could ever do everything perfect
enough for it to finally work for you
and just take imperfect bold courageous
action
towards putting your stuff together
and showing up
in your business
to put yourself out there to connect
with the people that you're meant to
impact
my friends i said this at the beginning
coaches change the world
and here's why
because they help direct people to those
goals
and if a coach can help impact a
thousand people
who knows what's going to happen next
who knows the kind of impact those
people would have who knows the type of
policies and government that would be
created
yeah
who knows
the type of
legacy that they're gonna leave
the wealth that's created
if you coach somebody
and they end up increasing their income
and you broke poverty off that family
life
that's what happened with me and my
family when we first found
a coach and a mentor that helped my mom
and i
19 years ago
my mom was already successful in
business by the way which is
awesome like it was like
she had already already made
millions in business
years ago and we had found this coach in
this mentor online
her name is danny johnson and
she's a personal development network
marketing and kind of money and finance
coach
and this is where we found
our first exposure to coaches and
coaching and the impact that coaches can
have on the world to change their life
and that and and i ended up working for
danny actually i had i ended up being an
employee this is my first
full-time job
my first job was actually working for my
mom
my next job i was working for this guy
tom challen create wealth while having a
life
and then working for danny johnson and i
was doing videos and so that was a
course creator and a coach that i ended
up working for
helping
to build products and to build programs
and then to market and get more
customers and so then by that that sort
of birthed and evolved into what i'm
doing helping other course creators and
coaches scale their businesses
okay my friends
and so here's the thing is that that
impact of us showing up and learning
from a coach from a trainer from a
mentor had so much impact on the life of
my mom and i back in the day
that now
we're building our business our our our
own businesses separately
okay
and so my mom's got her inner circle
she's got her stocks in crypto
helping people attract the right clients
make more money and live the life of
their dreams and she's been doing that
forever
and i'm helping people grow their own
online coaching and course business how
to do the growth strategy
marketing side of things the real the
real nitty-gritty side of it the real
the ai side of it and and and this is
copy you know that i'm using for an
offer that i've been building
for coaches and course creators because
i believe that coaches and course
creators change the world
and so my friends
keep your vision bigger than just your
own personal experience
keep your vision bigger than just what's
going on in your own life
and start to have the impact that you
can have by launching your coaching
program by stepping up and no longer
making excuses
motivation is fleeting but
self-discipline is what will keep you on
track and by disciplining yourself and
by taking
personal responsibility over where your
life is at not blaming anyone else for
what's going on and not making excuses
for why you can't and actually doing
something
it gives you an opportunity to show up
and to have the impact that you want to
have and to make a whole stinking lot of
money
all right my friends listen
if you've been listening to this today
and you're like i'd love to coach with
you jeremiah check out the one-on-one
coaching over at my website let's work
together
maybe you're not ready for that level
check out the one dollar trial that i
have all of my courses at my website
again this is only going on until april
5th
sometimes we do these
maybe once or twice a year
we do a dollar trial
but my friends don't
i'm gonna actually say this
don't make the stupid choice
of waiting
until the future
to take action in your business in life
because if you do that you will
constantly be waiting
i've met some people that did that
they learned what i'm teaching you now
10 years ago
and they haven't done a thing with it
they're sitting in a job they hate
they're complaining they're blaming
their boss and their wife and the
government for why they can't do what i
just showed you
and they're mad as heck at everybody
don't be like that
don't be an angry grump
don't be somebody who's always
complaining all the time
don't be somebody who's always making
excuses for why you can't
it starts with the first step now i've
shown you a whole lot but jasper ai is a
tool that'll get you started thinkific
is a tool that gets you started
squarespace are tools that'll get you
started if you coach with me i'll be
able to identify the exact next step
that you need to do and we'll be able to
work together to build your dreams
together
if you go through my courses i'll walk
you through in the training step by step
everything that you need to build a
multi-million dollar coaching business
and to get to twenty thousand dollars a
month
choice is yours you can either get
started
or keep complaining and making excuses i
don't really have tolerance for people
that complain and make excuses around me
personally
i don't help those people i don't work
with them
i just i don't i don't spend time with
them i don't have friends that are that
way
by the way who are the friends that
you're hanging out with
how are they influencing your brain how
are they influencing your thought life
how are they influencing
the choices you make
are you letting complainers tell you how
to live your life
are you letting critics
knock you down and control your thought
patterns
or are you the one
making the decisions to step out
courageously and do whatever it takes to
reach your goals and listen i'm not
talking about when i say whatever it
takes i'm not talking about
abusing people manipulating people being
coercive
or harmful please hear me on that
i've been around enough of that crap
in my life
that i'm not
okay with
any of it
in this business
i won't work with people that that
operate that way
i have literally canceled multi-million
dollar contracts
with people that act that way
this guy won't let it around me
choice is yours are you tolerating
negativity in your life
are you tolerating
people that always whine and complain
and moan about how nothing's going well
and they don't take personal
responsibility are you doing that in
your life
you might want to take account of that
and you might want to ask yourself why
am i operating this way why am i
spending time with people like this
and it'll really point to what's been
stopping you and limiting you and
keeping you stuck from reaching your
goals
your mindset is what it takes my friends
what you believe about yourself what you
believe you're capable of
what you believe is possible for you
i see way too often people
going out there launching their
businesses trying to make change in the
world
and they don't believe in themselves
because their their brother told them
that they shouldn't be building it and
they waited 10 years to still complain
and do nothing and they finally became
just like their grumpy old brother
and then i see other people
in six months
in three months even
start to make traction start to have
their first coaching client start to
gain
more experience and more traction in
their life my friends
the choice is yours
what are you gonna let influence you
what are you gonna let stop you
sometimes we need help in this area i do
i do mindset coaching with people and we
work through some of these issues
now i'm not a therapist
i recommend people check out the site
betterhelp.com or even
talkspace.com
if you don't have the money to do so i'm
serious check this out this one really
helped me for free
seven cups
need somebody to talk to counselors that
are standing by
it's not therapy
but it's free counsel
from people that are going through the
same things you are and you can talk to
different people they listen to you
they they they don't really give you
advice but they help you work through
stuff
for free
my friends
there's no excuses today in this world
there's no reason
for you to say i can't do it
a lot of people like well therapy is uh
is a privilege with the internet not
anymore
not anymore everybody's got a cell phone
and seven cups is actually strategically
designed to work on all cell phones
i actually checked that out they have
such apps that actually work on the most
basic of cell phones the android phones
that you can get anybody can get
there's great books out there
on amazon
how to do the work by nicole epras one
that i'd really recommend you starting
with
how to do the work recognize
your patterns heal your past and create
yourself and then what you do is you
read that book
another great one is
the body keeps the score this is a
really good one
brain mind and body healing of trauma
and then you write down and journal
what you come up with from that
and then you can go on seven cups
or on better help
and talk to somebody about what you came
to the conclusion of when you discovered
and unlocked what was stopping you
and you can find somebody to help you
that's how i did it that was the journey
that i went on
my friends the choice is yours what's
stopping you from reaching your goals
what's stopping you from launching your
coaching program
i just don't have enough time to do it
my friends there's it's not a lack of
time it's a lack of understanding of
systems of time management
and systems of time management are no
longer just franklin covey and a planner
i did a whole podcast episode about time
management for entrepreneurs
last week
go listen to it
or maybe two weeks ago
go listen to
it it's going to radically change your
life and what you do with time
choice is yours
what's gonna what are you gonna let stop
you
certainly not the skill sets
you know how to learn skill sets
you got youtube there's over 106 almost
160 episodes of this podcast
that you can listen to
i have thousands of videos on youtube
if you go to youtube
and type in
any topic
imposter syndrome jeremiah krakowski
these are videos where i talk about
imposter syndrome
jeremiah krakowski
all these videos are on here
facebook ads jeremiah krakowski
social media jeremiah you see what i'm
saying even if you're not buying my
courses which by the way you can buy
them for a dollar i think everybody has
a dollar and they can actually go
through and and grab that bundle
if you're listening to this before the
deadline if you aren't
go through these videos
go through my podcast that's at my
website and on podcast apps everywhere
on apple music and on spotify stitcher
youtube
yeah time management that actually works
for busy entrepreneurs
these episodes are going to walk you
through everything that you need
overcoming perfectionism
easy guide to successful opt-ins and
landing pages courageously communicating
expectations growing your email list
launching your own business
time management
hundreds of episodes different topics we
even talk about stuff like nfts and
motivation and and upcoming technology
finding your niche
self-discipline different things like
that my friends
what are you waiting for
the choice is yours
plug in
get the training you need get the
support you need get the help you need
plug into my grow your life facebook
group
there's almost two thousand people that
are course creators and coaches in there
that are learning how to build their
course and coaching business
the choice is
yours what are you waiting for my
friends listen if you're thinking about
doing one-on-one coaching with me
if you're listening to this before the
sale
and you schedule
a free 45-minute discovery call with me
at my website you go to 101 coaching
you scroll down to the bottom you click
on schedule a free 40-minute discovery
call if you schedule it
before april 5th
i'll honor this rate for you
after that it's the new rate
okay
you can lock that until march 1st 2025
three years
if you schedule it before then i'll
honor that rate and we can talk about
your business we can talk about what
it's going to take to take your business
to the next level and how we can work
together
okay the call will actually take place
after april 5th but at least get in the
scheduling before then okay
and i'll always give you an opportunity
before i raise any of my coaching rates
again
to be able to do the same type of thing
this is not the last time i'm gonna
raise this rate
after this is gonna be ten thousand
dollars in a couple months
just fyi
it's gonna be
double what it is now
in about three three
months maybe less than that maybe two
months yeah
what are you waiting for my friend
schedule a discovery call i'd love to
talk with you and i'd love to help you
build your business
grow your life everybody and we'll talk
soon have a good one